imagenomic.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy

**LAST UPDATED: November 9, 2017**

**IMAGENOMIC PRIVACY POLICY**

Imagenomic, LLC is concerned about privacy issues and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with information that we collect  through the websites operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy, through the software products made available for use or purchase by us, through our social media pages that link to this Privacy Policy and through HTML-formatted email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the "  **Services** ") . By providing Personal Information to us or using the Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Personal Information We May Collect**

" **Personal Information** " is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable person  , including: 

  * Name

  * Postal address (including billing and shipping addresses) 

  * Telephone number 

  * Email address 

  * Employer name or organization name (if applicable) 

  * Profile picture and biographical information 

  * Social media account ID 

We may use a third-party payment service to process payments made through the Services.  If you wish to make a payment through the Services, your Personal Information may be collected by such third party and not by us, and will be subject to the third party's privacy policy, rather than this Privacy Policy.  We have no control over, and are not responsible for, this third party's collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information. 

If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**How We May Collect Personal Information**

We and our service providers may collect Personal Information in a variety of ways, including: 

  * **Through the Services** : We may collect Personal Information through the Services, such as when you download, register account, sign up for a newsletter or make a purchase with us. 

  * **From Other Sources** : We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, such as public databases; social media platforms; and people with whom you are friends or otherwise connected on social media platforms. For example, if you elect to connect your social media account to your Website account, certain Personal Information from your social media account will be shared with us, which may include Personal Information that is part of your profile or your friend' profiles. 

**How We May Use Personal Information**

We may use Personal Information: 

  * To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, such as to send you newsletters. 

  * To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Services and changes to our terms, conditions and policies. 

  * To complete and fulfill your purchase, for example, to process your payments, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service. 

  * To authenticate your product license. 

  * To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you. 

  * To personalize your experience on the Services by presenting products and offers tailored to you. 

  * To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your Personal Information, so we suggest that you read these rules carefully. 

  * To facilitate social sharing functionality. 

  * To allow you to send messages to a friend through the Services.By using this functionality, you are telling us that you are entitled to use and provide us with your friend's name and email address. 

  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our Services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities. 

  * As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

**How Personal Information May Be Disclosed**

Your Personal Information may be disclosed: 

To our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing and other similar services. 

To third parties sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions. 

To identify you to anyone to whom you send messages through the Services. 

By you, on message boards, forums, gallery pages, chat, profile pages and blogs and other services to which you are able to post information, photographs and materials. Please note that any information you post or disclose through these services will become public information and may be available to users of the Services and to the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, on the Services. 

To your friends associated with your social media account, to other users of the Services and to your social media account provider, in connection with your social sharing activity, such as if you connect your social media account to your Services account or log-into your Services account from your social media account. By connecting your Services account and your social media account, you authorize us to share information with your social media account provider, and you understand that the use of the information we share will be governed by the social media site's privacy policy.If you do not want your Personal Information shared with other users or with your social media account provider, please do not connect your social media account with your Services account, and do not participate in social sharing on the Services. 

To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. 

**OTHER INFORMATION**

**Other Information We May Collect**

" **Other Information** " is any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as: 

  * Browser and device information 

  * Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies 

  * Demographic information and other information provided by you 

  * Diagnostic and usage information 

  * Aggregated information 

**How We May Collect Other Information**

We and our third party service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including: 

**Through your browser or device** : Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system name and version, device manufacturer and model, language, Internet browser type and version and the name and version of the Services you are using. We use this information to ensure that the Services function properly. 

**Using cookies** : Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Services, pages visited, language preferences and other anonymous traffic data. We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively and to personalize your experience while using the Services. We also gather statistical information about use of the Services in order to continually improve their design and functionality, understand how they are used and assist us with resolving questions about them. Cookies further allow us to select which of our advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Services. We may also use cookies in online advertising to track responses to our advertisements. We do not track your use of third-party websites or services. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. You may also wish to refer to  [_http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html_](https://clck.yandex.ru/redir/nWO_r1F33ck?data=NnBZTWRhdFZKOHQxUjhzSWFYVGhXVzlVdU94M2c2SW5SOU82aDJiXzlHRmpPRTJoS0ZnYVhLNGRDWS14UXZZOWNaLXpFWDlvV2NyUm9OZ2hSSTNMX2R5VU5mNVJKQTBqRWQzTE40SlA1M0E3ZEFFdGJIaWxURHNudnZzcy1LS0NIMVZTSVdIUlVheDIzT3JmUFRXbG9n&b64e=2&sign=26560cb58aa461feca2bd8d1950832f2&keyno=17) . If, however, you do not accept these cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Services. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer and you may need to log in every time you visit the applicable Services. You also may not receive advertising or other offers from us that are relevant to your interests and needs. 

**Using pixel tags and**   **other similar technologies** : Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Services to, among other things, track the actions of users of the Services (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about use of the Services and response rates. 

We use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and other, similar technologies to collect information about website use anonymously and reports trends, without identifying individual visitors. To learn more about Google Analytics, including how to opt out of it, visit  [_https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout_](https://clck.yandex.ru/redir/nWO_r1F33ck?data=NnBZTWRhdFZKOHRaTENSMFc4S0VQRVBVblpqVmE4SnlUU0h0M0huTU1zTkY3Z1dpU2J3emxOVFRPUl9RTkdOX0xIX2xrTnBBdjM2S0k4MC1ZUW1GemxRVUdTSGktWmEzR3VaRTl3V2k0T2FMTkd5eTZhdGJVX3VKRUwtcmxob1Q&b64e=2&sign=bc79ddc12ff827eb3a14b95c1d25ecbb&keyno=17).

**Using Adobe Flash technology (including Flash Local Shared Objects ("Flash LSOs")) and other similar technologies** : We may use Flash LSOs and other technologies to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of the Services.If you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your computer, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained in the  [ _Website Storage Settings Panel_ ](https://clck.yandex.ru/redir/nWO_r1F33ck?data=NnBZTWRhdFZKOHQxUjhzSWFYVGhXUmtqMWgxTnZmTTlxc294a0JQVzNKalpxMXFGS3JXb0hzREtkNGg4VDhCalF3Tno4WnZCcVB2Y2Q3dE0zUW9SYVR6LXNHOEN0aW5ZY0g3aTNnb2hNMUd0MXIyT085YU1NcmV3MkljTlVLRnczemNTT1Fjd2ZSbDVHNnVFMHpucHFBdThzZWxxODVady03VFVsQS1ieHhCYTdYZENNTVRSTHdkU2ZuNDRrVGlGMkdWa1Z2aDU2eVBkeEk3c1RoZDhUdw&b64e=2&sign=2830aade1d5942be08e9d03128644ea7&keyno=17) . You can also control Flash LSOs by going to the  [ _Global Storage Settings Panel_ ](https://clck.yandex.ru/redir/nWO_r1F33ck?data=NnBZTWRhdFZKOHQxUjhzSWFYVGhXUmtqMWgxTnZmTTlxc294a0JQVzNKalpxMXFGS3JXb0hzREtkNGg4VDhCalF3Tno4WnZCcVB2Y2Q3dE0zUW9SYVR6LXNHOEN0aW5ZY0g3aTNnb2hNMUd0MXIyT085YU1NcmV3MkljTlVLRnczemNTT1Fjd2ZSbmc4ekY5OGR0TXVuYnFXejZnemU5S25kbG1hRlNrWnRSR2RhY1NRdlNBY1Y0RHc3Y2lOdnVsbi1LVmR1ekhQN0trZXQzaHAzQXpjQQ&b64e=2&sign=748674188880b3636f457ce58df60822&keyno=17)  and following the instructions (which may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred to "information" on the Macromedia site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your computer without your being asked, and (for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the operator of the page you are on at the time). Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash applications used in connection with the Services or our online content. 

**IP Address** : Your "  **IP Address** " is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user accesses the Services, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. Collecting IP Addresses is standard practice and is done automatically by many websites, applications and other services. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating usage levels of the Services, helping diagnose server problems and administering the Services. 

**From you** : Information such as your preferred means of communication is collected when you voluntarily provide it. Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not personally identify you. 

**By aggregating information** : Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you or any other user of the Services (for example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code). 

**How We May Use and Disclose Other Information**

We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use it for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. 

In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined. 

**THIRD PARTY SERVICES**

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site or service to which the Services link. The inclusion of a link on the Services does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service by us or by our affiliates. 

**SECURITY**

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization.Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us in accordance with the  _"Contact Us"_  section below. 

**CHOICES AND ACCESS**

If you no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out of receiving these marketing-related emails by following the instructions contained in each such email. If you opt out, we may still send you important administrative messages, from which you cannot opt-out. 

If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, or delete Personal Information that you have provided to us, you may contact us at  _mail@imagenomic.com_ . In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have it suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of it.For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. 

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting such change or deletion.There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed. 

**RETENTION PERIOD**

We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

**USE OF SERVICES BY MINORS**

The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that these individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Services. 

**CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER**

The Services are controlled and operated by us from the United States and are not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States.   Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and, by using the Services, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules from those of your country. 

**SENSITIVE INFORMATION**

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (  _e.g._ , Social Security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Services or otherwise to us. 

**UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may change this Privacy Policy. The "  _LAST UPDATED_ " legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services. Your use of the Services following these changes means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at  _mail@imagenomic.com_ .Because email communications are not always secure, please do not include credit card or other sensitive information in your emails to us.
